  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0706B-A">
    The ABSDF is an anti-government student organization operating on Myanmar-Thai border sine November 1988.
    According to a latest official disclosure, a total of 15 anti-government ethnic armed groups have made peace with government, leaving only one, KNU, still in insurgency.
    ``As you can see, looking at events of last week, government, rather than heeding call for dialogue, is instead adopting a more confrontational attitude,'' Wiedemann said.
    Q: In November '96 SLORC launched a tourism campaign called ``Visit Myanmar Year.''
    SUU KYI: The government appears to be more interested in stamping out political activity than drug addiction.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0706B-B">
    &UR;  &LR; To do business overseas, especially in cudgel-wielding dictatorships, savvy executive adopts a three-point strategy: 1) See No Evil, 2) Hear No Evil, 3) Speak No Evil.
    In words of ruling junta, Burma is one of most pleasant places created by Mother Nature.
    Yes, Rangoon cracked down on protests in 1988, killing thousands to restore order.
    Already some companies have retreated from Burma on moral grounds.
    It ended operations in Burma last year because of threats of a worldwide consumer boycott.
    It is too early to draw definitive conclusions about success of our policy toward China or Burma.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0706B-C">
    He added that armed men demanded that Myanmar government release all political prisoners, recognize results of 1990 general election and reshuffle government.
    After a 25-hour tense standoff, five Myanmar armed men Saturday ended their siege of Myanmar Embassy and freed all 38 hostages before they were flown to Myanmar border in Ratchaburi in company of Thai Deputy Foreign Minister Sukhumbhand Paribatra.
    Although noninterference in internal affairs of member states is a founding principle of ASEAN, cross-border flow of narcotics, HIV, and refugees into Thailand demonstrates folly of pretending that Burma's ASEAN neighbors are not affected by junta's misrule.
  </UPDATE>
