  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0726F-A">
    Thomas E. Patterson, a presidential campaign scholar at Harvard, says Gore has to distinguish himself from Clinton with considerable delicacy to avoid appearing disloyal.
    Kathy Sullivan, incoming chairwoman of Democratic Party in New Hampshire, state planning to hold nation's first presidential primary in 2000, warned that Democrats in New Hampshire aren't looking for Gore to condemn Clinton.
    Gore's delicate balancing act between loyalty and independence recalls challenges faced by Vice President George Bush as he prepared to launch his 1988 campaign to succeed Ronald Reagan and Vice President Hubert Humphrey as he sought to succeed Lyndon B. Johnson in 1968.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0726F-B">
    "I welcome new shape of this campaign," Gore said.
    ``Vice President Al Gore has demonstrated time and time again he is dedicated to people of United Statesbe it reducing gun violence, protecting our environment, bolstering patients rights, safeguarding a woman's right to choose or reforming public education,'' said Feinstein in a statement released Wednesday.
    The Hispanic endorsements of Gore may have taken some of sting out of decision by Friends of Earth, an influential environmental group, to back former Sen. Bill Bradley of New Jersey, Gore's sole competitor for 2000 Democratic presidential campaign.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0726F-C">
    Delay will resign from present office on July 15 to replace Tony Coelho, former California congressman who was hired by Gore a year ago to lead campaign.
    He called Gore Wednesday night with his resignation.
    Until Wednesday, Gore's campaign had been run from high-rent offices on K Street in Washington, corridor favored by lobbying and law firms that wield so much influence in nation's capital.
    Critics have suggested that campaign move is little more than a stunt by a presidential candidate who, as vice president, senator, congressman and son of a senator, has spent virtually his entire life in Washington.
  </UPDATE>
