  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0727G-A">
    According to motions released Tuesday, Marianne Gingrich's attorney, John Mayoue, also wants to take a deposition from unnamed representatives of GOPAC and Friends of Newt Gingrich campaign committee, for which Gaylord also worked.
    On Sept. 29, 33-year-old congressional aid Callista Bisek is scheduled to answer questions under oath about her relationship with Newt Gingrich.
    Gingrich seemed as if a ``great burden had been lifted from his shoulders,'' said Matt Glavin, director of Southeastern Legal Foundation in Atlanta, who spoke to Gingrich night he announced that he would not run for speaker and who was present at Monday dinner speech.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0727G-B">
    And it jolted many of Gingrich's colleagues still in Congress, fueling an already bubbling debate over impact of Gingrich's divorce on his unofficial role in Republican Party.
    But Marianne Gingrich says she and her husband were living together in a Marietta, Ga., condo.
    Marianne Gingrich, 48, is chairwoman of Red Cross' Northwest Metro Service Center.
    She plans to be in a Washington courtroom next week when attorneys for Bisek, 33, will try to persuade a judge to toss out Marianne Gingrich's demand that Bisek answer questions and turn over documents related to her relationship to Newt Gingrich, 56.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0727G-C">
    On Thursday, accusations of wrongdoing and mining of dirt in former U.S. House speaker's divorce case gave way to a secret settlement between Gingrich and his wife of 18 years, Marianne Gingrich.
    A sedate Marianne Gingrich, who did attend hearing, had only this to say about often bitter eight-month-long divorce process: ``It's been a difficult period of time.''
    Marianne Gingrich plans to continue her work with Red Cross and various charity groups.
    Chuck Clay, chairman of Georgia Republican Party, said divorce settlement will likely make it easier for Gingrich to return to public eye in a political setting.
  </UPDATE>
