  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0736H-A">
    The February sweeps end Wednesday night, so it's time for a very special, all-daytime and early evening remembrance of month that was ...&LR;   &LR; ``Extra'' hired a forensics expert, Dr. Laurence Kobilinski of John Jay College of Criminal Justice in New York, to determine that women's panties on department-store shelves are often soiled.
    _ &LR;   &LR; Oprah Winfrey took her show to Bahamas for a week.
    As disappointing as ``David and Lisa'' is, it would be too bad if it became ammunition in growing Oprah backlash.
    Oprah Winfrey and Kate Forte, executive producers.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0736H-B">
    &LR;  &QL; (Adds: GLF-TIGER; GLF-NELSON; and BKN-ROCKETS.) &LR;  &QL; (The ``HNS'' tag appears in all sluglines.) &LR;  &QL; For Thursday: POLITICAL NEWS (``p'' category) BUSH-McCAIN (Greenville, S.C.)John McCain sharpens his claim that his success has alarmed Republican Party's hierarchy and its lobbyist friends who back George W. Bush.
    By CLAY ROBISON.
    (Already filed.) WASHINGTON NEWS (``w'' category) HIGH-TECH-WORKERS (Washington)Three prominent Republican senatorsOrrin Hatch of Utah, Phil Gramm of Texas and Spencer Abraham of Michiganintroduce a bill that would boost number of visas for high-tech foreign workers to 195,000 for next three years, up 80,000 from current total.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0736H-C">
    Gore is first politician invited to television stage of Oprah Winfrey in Chicago.
    Reacting to a new Federal Trade Commission report criticizing Hollywood for targeting children with violent products, Gore said they would ask entertainment industry for a voluntary "cease- fire" in marketing inappropriate movies, video games and music to children.
    CAMPAIGN FINANCE (Washington)Minnesota Gov. Jesse Ventura joins Sens. John McCain, R-Ariz., and Russell Feingold, D-Wis., in lobbying for campaign finance reform during an election in which unregulated contributions to Republican and Democratic parties have skyrocketed.
    Freedman helped Stanford win informal national college championship, then participated in Ride Across America.
  </UPDATE>
