  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0743J-A">
    ISTANBUL (Turkey), August 21 (Xinhua) -- Blaze in a refinery in western Turkey has been under control after strong efforts made by foreign rescue experts, a Turkish official said on Saturday.
    Two hours later, rescue workers finally walked away, leaving behind anguished cries of onlookers and what rescue workers were certain were two corpses buried in rubble.
    Turkey and Israel have forged a strong strategic partnership over last few years, and Israel is evidently anxious to show that it can be a good friend when Turkey is in need.
    Turkey sits atop some of world's most unstable geology.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0743J-B">
    Some of them were sent here by ambulances or helicopters from other quake-hit areas where public hospitals were demolished and makeshift field hospitals, set up by medical staff from internal or foreign countries, did not have necessary facilities to deal with some serious injuries.
    He said nearly one-sixth of 3,000 apartment units he built had collapsed in quake.
    Despite rescue efforts like one today in Cinarcik, search for survivors was winding down.
    Out in hard-hit cities like Golcuk and Izmit, heavy earthmoving equipment was at work at many sites, marking an effective end to delicate rescue efforts of previous days.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0743J-C">
    Turkey's Daily News reported on Thursday that an additional 150, 000 people live in cramped prefabricated homes that are extremely hot in summer and bitterly cold in winter.
    Some victims who survived disaster complained about their grievance, saying that "the state doesn't care about us."
    Seismologists have warned that aftershocks and tremors may shake Turkey for months and possibly years.
    A new report by country's largest business federation describes that quake as ``the biggest one of 20th century affecting a large, populated industrialized area.''
    ``The increased uncertainty will negatively affect all economic activity in Turkey,'' report said.
  </UPDATE>
