  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0740I-A">
    Pilots Bertrand Piccard from Switzerland and Wim Verstraeten from Belgium, plus flight engineer Andy Elson from Britain, were planning to depart around 8:30 a.m. (0730 GMT) from Chateau d'Oex, in western Switzerland, aboard Breitling Orbiter II.
    Their Cable and Wireless balloon, which launched from Spain on Feb. 17, has broken balloon endurance records for time aloft.
    Bertrand Piccard of Switzerland and Briton Brian Jones climbed out of hi-tech gondola of Breitling Orbiter 3 balloon to break off some of icicles with an ice pick on Thursday.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0740I-B">
    The prospect that Breitling's crew, Bertrand Piccard and Brian Jones, may succeed where all others have failed seemed more promising with each passing hour.
    The Breitling ground team in Geneva forecast that huge Swiss-registered balloon would complete its circuit of Earth on Saturday, somewhere in North Africa.
    The Breitling balloon faced staggering problems to get this far.
    China gave last-minute permission, but only on condition that balloon remain south of 26th parallel.
    Sometimes balloon crawled at 20 miles an hour, but in stretches where crew could exploit jet streams, Breitling sped at more than 100 miles an hour.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0740I-C">
    GENEVA, March 24 (Xinhua) -- The International Olympic Committee said Wednesday that they will award Olympic Order to balloonists Bertrand Piccard and Brian Jones who are first to circumnavigate world in a balloon.
    Piccard of Switzerland and Briton Jones joined first man on moon, American astronaut Neil Armstrong, and other aeronautical legends such as Charles Lindbergh as recipients of higly-valued award.
    Unlike Piccard and Jones, though, Uliassi is flying in an unpressurized crew compartment.
    The Egyptian government spokesman, Nabil Osman, said that weather-driven changes in plans for balloon's landing had slowed military's plans for swift recovery of crew.
  </UPDATE>
