<?xml version="1.0" standalone="no"?>

<!DOCTYPE DUC2007UPDATETASKSUBMISSION SYSTEM "duc2007updatetasksubmission.dtd">

<DUC2007UPDATETASKSUBMISSION SYSID="IIPDrexelU" TASK="UPDATE">

  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0703A-A">
    BONN, April 20 (Xinhua) -- Private investors are set to benefit from 1999 introduction of single European currency, euro, thanks to expanded investment opportunities, reduced currency risks, and rising competitions, German central bank Bundesbank said Monday.
    Moreover, investors are also set to benefit from reduced transaction costs and improved market transparency resulting from heated competitions among financial institutions after advent of euro, Bundesbank said.
    The European Union member states are required to completely replace their own national currencies with Euro from January 1, 2002.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0703A-B">
    BANGKOK, November 10 (Xinhua) -- Thailand is considering using European single currency, euro, in country's foreign reserves, Nation reported Tuesday.
    A special task force will study impact of euro on country's official reserves in a bid to help stem volatility of U.S. dollar and Japanese yen.
    However, arrival of euro is likely to reduce Thailand's trading volume with other countries significantly, official said.
    The total cost of introducing euro is estimated to be at 1 to 1.5 percent of gross domestic product of 11 euro countries.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0703A-C">
    "Romania's Central Bank (BNR) and country's commercial banks fear little about introduction of euro and will easily adapt to it," BNR Foreign Currency Director George Mucibabici told a recent colloquium on euro in Bucharest.
    BNR and Romanian commercial banks that want to perform euro services will have to open accounts in euro by January 4, 1999, first scheduled day of euro use, and inform their foreign partners.
    BNR indicative exchange rates will be modified to include euro instead of current European single currency, ECU.
    The daily exchange rates released by central bank would include single currency, too, he said.
  </UPDATE>

  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0706B-A">
    The ABSDF is an anti-government student organization operating on Myanmar-Thai border sine November 1988.
    According to a latest official disclosure, a total of 15 anti-government ethnic armed groups have made peace with government, leaving only one, KNU, still in insurgency.
    ``As you can see, looking at events of last week, government, rather than heeding call for dialogue, is instead adopting a more confrontational attitude,'' Wiedemann said.
    Q: In November '96 SLORC launched a tourism campaign called ``Visit Myanmar Year.''
    SUU KYI: The government appears to be more interested in stamping out political activity than drug addiction.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0706B-B">
    To do business overseas, especially in cudgel-wielding dictatorships, savvy executive adopts a three-point strategy: 1) See No Evil, 2) Hear No Evil, 3) Speak No Evil.
    In words of ruling junta, Burma is one of most pleasant places created by Mother Nature.
    Yes, Rangoon cracked down on protests in 1988, killing thousands to restore order.
    Already some companies have retreated from Burma on moral grounds.
    It ended operations in Burma last year because of threats of a worldwide consumer boycott.
    It is too early to draw definitive conclusions about success of our policy toward China or Burma.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0706B-C">
    He added that armed men demanded that Myanmar government release all political prisoners, recognize results of 1990 general election and reshuffle government.
    After a 25-hour tense standoff, five Myanmar armed men Saturday ended their siege of Myanmar Embassy and freed all 38 hostages before they were flown to Myanmar border in Ratchaburi in company of Thai Deputy Foreign Minister Sukhumbhand Paribatra.
    Although noninterference in internal affairs of member states is a founding principle of ASEAN, cross-border flow of narcotics, HIV, and refugees into Thailand demonstrates folly of pretending that Burma's ASEAN neighbors are not affected by junta's misrule.
  </UPDATE>

  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0711C-A">
    LOS ANGELES, October 19 (Xinhua) -- Business seemed as usual at Microsoft headquarters on first day of U.S. government's antitrust trial against this software giant.
    On Monday in Washington D.C., federal government and 20 states kicked off trial that accused Microsoft of illegal activities, including bullying competitors.
    He asserted that Microsoft repeatedly offered IBM better terms and prices for Windows if it favored Microsoft products ranging from so-called office productivity applications to its Internet browsing software.
    Much of detailed, company-by-company information on prices to makers for Microsoft's industry-standard Windows operating system was submitted in previous testimony.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0711C-B">
    As a result, on Friday evening Microsoft faxed a several-page settlement offer to Justice Department and 19 state attorneys general who are suing Microsoft.
    Fierce competition is one thing, government says, but voluminous record including volumes of e-mail, internal Microsoft documents and witness testimony show Microsoft to have been an arm-twisting monopolist, whose corporate behavior stifled competition and harmed consumers.
    Some antitrust experts say Lessig brief may give Jackson legal blueprint he needs for concluding that Microsoft did violate tying law.
    Klein saw another reason to hold up Microsoft case as an example.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0711C-C">
    Microsoft Chairman Bill Gates said immediately after ruling that, as expected, company would appeal.
    The government says that splitting Microsoft would prevent Windows system, that runs on over 80 percent of personal computers, from being used to force companies and consumers to use other Microsoft products.
    The company's appeal could bypass normal appeals court process and go straight to Supreme Court under a mechanism available in major antitrust cases.
    Several of legal experts said Thursday that they saw little support for Microsoft's suggestion that judge was relying on antitrust concepts that are out of step with fast-moving computer business.
  </UPDATE>

  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0716D-A">
    The Age -- Australian conservationists and traditional aboriginal owners threatened to blockade development of huge Jabiluka uranium mine in country's vast Kakadu National Park, which is on World Heritage List, after federal government approved mining plan for Jabilika mine yesterday.
    Resources Minister Warwick Parer said estimates indicated Jabiluka mine contains about 19.5 million tons of ore, which could provide more than 90,400 tons of uranium oxide.
    "Jabiluka means Australia could become leading world uranium oxide supplier," Parer said in a statement.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0716D-B">
    CANBERRA, November 25 (Xinhua) -- Australia faces international embarrassment over Jabiluka uranium mine, with a U.N. committee Wednesday demanding mine be scrapped to prevent it endangering surrounding Kakadu World Heritage area.
    "The mission has concluded that Kakadu National Park is exposed to a number of serious threats which are placing it under both ascertained and potential danger," bureau said in a report after it sent a mission to Australia to examine claims by conservation groups that Kakadu (National Park in Northern Territory) was under threat from Jabiluka.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0716D-C">
    The Australian: -- The Australian government's environmental report on Jabiluka uranium mine (located in Kakadu Natural Park), to be released Thursday, found area is not under threat and attacked a UNESCO report that said Kakadu Natural Park was in danger.
    Hill said Australia's response to report "clearly demonstrated that there is no basis to including Kakadu National Park on in-danger list".
    The findings of mission report were inconsistent with fact Ranger uranium mine, less than 20 km from Jabiluka had operated for 20 years with no adverse impact on Kakadu.
  </UPDATE>

  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0721E-A">
    The New York Times said in an editorial for Tuesday, April 6: Russell Henderson's decision to plead guilty to kidnapping and murder of Matthew Shepard is little consolation to Shepard family, but it provides an appropriately severe sentence for one whose apparent anti-gay hatred led him to destroy a young life.
    ``Aaron McKinney, he pulled out a gun and told Matthew Shepard to give him his wallet,'' continued Henderson, who said that while he drove his friend beat Shepard.
    The stress on Shepard family was so great, she continued, that within a month of Matthew's funeral, his paternal grandfather died.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0721E-B">
    Henderson pleaded guilty to murder this spring to avoid a death penalty.
    Shepard's mother, Judy, sat with several friends opposite several of McKinney's relatives, including his father, Bill McKinney.
    Rerucha presented a chronology for night of Oct. 6, 1998, from Fireside Lounge, where McKinney and Henderson encountered Shepard, to beatings, which began as two drove Shepard around town and continued at fence.
    As a result, Tangeman told jury, McKinney ``becomes very, very upset and beats Matthew Shepard,'' prompted by memories of a sexual encounter forced upon him by an older boy when he was 7.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0721E-C">
    The prosecution had originally asked for death penalty for Aaron McKinney, 22, for killing Matthew Shepard, a 21-year-old college student, but later Shepard's parents agreed to spare him from lethal injection.
    The play ultimately questions whether Laramie, or nation, has changed as a result.
    In an interview, he said Shepard murder had changed some attitudes in Laramie, including those of friends of his who no longer use word ``fag'' to describe a gay man.
    ``After Matthew Shepard incident, there was a push for understanding, like we're going to face what happened in our community and we're going to change.''
  </UPDATE>

  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0726F-A">
    Thomas E. Patterson, a presidential campaign scholar at Harvard, says Gore has to distinguish himself from Clinton with considerable delicacy to avoid appearing disloyal.
    Kathy Sullivan, incoming chairwoman of Democratic Party in New Hampshire, state planning to hold nation's first presidential primary in 2000, warned that Democrats in New Hampshire aren't looking for Gore to condemn Clinton.
    Gore's delicate balancing act between loyalty and independence recalls challenges faced by Vice President George Bush as he prepared to launch his 1988 campaign to succeed Ronald Reagan and Vice President Hubert Humphrey as he sought to succeed Lyndon B. Johnson in 1968.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0726F-B">
    "I welcome new shape of this campaign," Gore said.
    ``Vice President Al Gore has demonstrated time and time again he is dedicated to people of United Statesbe it reducing gun violence, protecting our environment, bolstering patients rights, safeguarding a woman's right to choose or reforming public education,'' said Feinstein in a statement released Wednesday.
    The Hispanic endorsements of Gore may have taken some of sting out of decision by Friends of Earth, an influential environmental group, to back former Sen. Bill Bradley of New Jersey, Gore's sole competitor for 2000 Democratic presidential campaign.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0726F-C">
    Delay will resign from present office on July 15 to replace Tony Coelho, former California congressman who was hired by Gore a year ago to lead campaign.
    He called Gore Wednesday night with his resignation.
    Until Wednesday, Gore's campaign had been run from high-rent offices on K Street in Washington, corridor favored by lobbying and law firms that wield so much influence in nation's capital.
    Critics have suggested that campaign move is little more than a stunt by a presidential candidate who, as vice president, senator, congressman and son of a senator, has spent virtually his entire life in Washington.
  </UPDATE>

  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0727G-A">
    According to motions released Tuesday, Marianne Gingrich's attorney, John Mayoue, also wants to take a deposition from unnamed representatives of GOPAC and Friends of Newt Gingrich campaign committee, for which Gaylord also worked.
    On Sept. 29, 33-year-old congressional aid Callista Bisek is scheduled to answer questions under oath about her relationship with Newt Gingrich.
    Gingrich seemed as if a ``great burden had been lifted from his shoulders,'' said Matt Glavin, director of Southeastern Legal Foundation in Atlanta, who spoke to Gingrich night he announced that he would not run for speaker and who was present at Monday dinner speech.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0727G-B">
    And it jolted many of Gingrich's colleagues still in Congress, fueling an already bubbling debate over impact of Gingrich's divorce on his unofficial role in Republican Party.
    But Marianne Gingrich says she and her husband were living together in a Marietta, Ga., condo.
    Marianne Gingrich, 48, is chairwoman of Red Cross' Northwest Metro Service Center.
    She plans to be in a Washington courtroom next week when attorneys for Bisek, 33, will try to persuade a judge to toss out Marianne Gingrich's demand that Bisek answer questions and turn over documents related to her relationship to Newt Gingrich, 56.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0727G-C">
    On Thursday, accusations of wrongdoing and mining of dirt in former U.S. House speaker's divorce case gave way to a secret settlement between Gingrich and his wife of 18 years, Marianne Gingrich.
    A sedate Marianne Gingrich, who did attend hearing, had only this to say about often bitter eight-month-long divorce process: ``It's been a difficult period of time.''
    Marianne Gingrich plans to continue her work with Red Cross and various charity groups.
    Chuck Clay, chairman of Georgia Republican Party, said divorce settlement will likely make it easier for Gingrich to return to public eye in a political setting.
  </UPDATE>

  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0736H-A">
    The February sweeps end Wednesday night, so it's time for a very special, all-daytime and early evening remembrance of month that was ...   ``Extra'' hired a forensics expert, Dr. Laurence Kobilinski of John Jay College of Criminal Justice in New York, to determine that women's panties on department-store shelves are often soiled.
    Oprah Winfrey took her show to Bahamas for a week.
    As disappointing as ``David and Lisa'' is, it would be too bad if it became ammunition in growing Oprah backlash.
    Oprah Winfrey and Kate Forte, executive producers.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0736H-B">
    (Adds: GLF-TIGER; GLF-NELSON; and BKN-ROCKETS.) (The ``HNS'' tag appears in all sluglines.) For Thursday: POLITICAL NEWS (``p'' category) BUSH-McCAIN (Greenville, S.C.)John McCain sharpens his claim that his success has alarmed Republican Party's hierarchy and its lobbyist friends who back George W. Bush.
    By CLAY ROBISON.
    (Already filed.) WASHINGTON NEWS (``w'' category) HIGH-TECH-WORKERS (Washington)Three prominent Republican senatorsOrrin Hatch of Utah, Phil Gramm of Texas and Spencer Abraham of Michiganintroduce a bill that would boost number of visas for high-tech foreign workers to 195,000 for next three years, up 80,000 from current total.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0736H-C">
    Gore is first politician invited to television stage of Oprah Winfrey in Chicago.
    Reacting to a new Federal Trade Commission report criticizing Hollywood for targeting children with violent products, Gore said they would ask entertainment industry for a voluntary "cease- fire" in marketing inappropriate movies, video games and music to children.
    CAMPAIGN FINANCE (Washington)Minnesota Gov. Jesse Ventura joins Sens. John McCain, R-Ariz., and Russell Feingold, D-Wis., in lobbying for campaign finance reform during an election in which unregulated contributions to Republican and Democratic parties have skyrocketed.
    Freedman helped Stanford win informal national college championship, then participated in Ride Across America.
  </UPDATE>

  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0740I-A">
    Pilots Bertrand Piccard from Switzerland and Wim Verstraeten from Belgium, plus flight engineer Andy Elson from Britain, were planning to depart around 8:30 a.m. (0730 GMT) from Chateau d'Oex, in western Switzerland, aboard Breitling Orbiter II.
    Their Cable and Wireless balloon, which launched from Spain on Feb. 17, has broken balloon endurance records for time aloft.
    Bertrand Piccard of Switzerland and Briton Brian Jones climbed out of hi-tech gondola of Breitling Orbiter 3 balloon to break off some of icicles with an ice pick on Thursday.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0740I-B">
    The prospect that Breitling's crew, Bertrand Piccard and Brian Jones, may succeed where all others have failed seemed more promising with each passing hour.
    The Breitling ground team in Geneva forecast that huge Swiss-registered balloon would complete its circuit of Earth on Saturday, somewhere in North Africa.
    The Breitling balloon faced staggering problems to get this far.
    China gave last-minute permission, but only on condition that balloon remain south of 26th parallel.
    Sometimes balloon crawled at 20 miles an hour, but in stretches where crew could exploit jet streams, Breitling sped at more than 100 miles an hour.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0740I-C">
    GENEVA, March 24 (Xinhua) -- The International Olympic Committee said Wednesday that they will award Olympic Order to balloonists Bertrand Piccard and Brian Jones who are first to circumnavigate world in a balloon.
    Piccard of Switzerland and Briton Jones joined first man on moon, American astronaut Neil Armstrong, and other aeronautical legends such as Charles Lindbergh as recipients of higly-valued award.
    Unlike Piccard and Jones, though, Uliassi is flying in an unpressurized crew compartment.
    The Egyptian government spokesman, Nabil Osman, said that weather-driven changes in plans for balloon's landing had slowed military's plans for swift recovery of crew.
  </UPDATE>

  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0743J-A">
    ISTANBUL (Turkey), August 21 (Xinhua) -- Blaze in a refinery in western Turkey has been under control after strong efforts made by foreign rescue experts, a Turkish official said on Saturday.
    Two hours later, rescue workers finally walked away, leaving behind anguished cries of onlookers and what rescue workers were certain were two corpses buried in rubble.
    Turkey and Israel have forged a strong strategic partnership over last few years, and Israel is evidently anxious to show that it can be a good friend when Turkey is in need.
    Turkey sits atop some of world's most unstable geology.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0743J-B">
    Some of them were sent here by ambulances or helicopters from other quake-hit areas where public hospitals were demolished and makeshift field hospitals, set up by medical staff from internal or foreign countries, did not have necessary facilities to deal with some serious injuries.
    He said nearly one-sixth of 3,000 apartment units he built had collapsed in quake.
    Despite rescue efforts like one today in Cinarcik, search for survivors was winding down.
    Out in hard-hit cities like Golcuk and Izmit, heavy earthmoving equipment was at work at many sites, marking an effective end to delicate rescue efforts of previous days.
  </UPDATE>
  <UPDATE DOCSUBSET="D0743J-C">
    Turkey's Daily News reported on Thursday that an additional 150, 000 people live in cramped prefabricated homes that are extremely hot in summer and bitterly cold in winter.
    Some victims who survived disaster complained about their grievance, saying that "the state doesn't care about us."
    Seismologists have warned that aftershocks and tremors may shake Turkey for months and possibly years.
    A new report by country's largest business federation describes that quake as ``the biggest one of 20th century affecting a large, populated industrialized area.''
    ``The increased uncertainty will negatively affect all economic activity in Turkey,'' report said.
  </UPDATE>

</DUC2007UPDATETASKSUBMISSION>

